I have created two sets of installation processes for each tool needed in this course;
Eu criei dois conjuntos de processos de instalao para cada ferramenta necessria neste curso;
an express version, and the complete version.
uma verso expressa e a verso completa.
Since this course is targeted at experienced engineers, this section will provide
Como este curso destina-se a engenheiros experientes, esta seo fornecer
a streamlined, express version, of the installation instructions.
uma verso simplificada e expressa das instrues de instalao.
This course includes installation instructions for the
Este curso inclui instrues de instalao para os
two main operating systems widely used today; Windows, and Mac OS X.
dois principais sistemas operacionais amplamente usados atualmente; Windows e Mac OS X.
For each operating system, I will provide the list of tools, where to download them,
Para cada sistema operacional, fornecerei a lista de ferramentas, onde baix-las
and any deviations from the default choices during the installation process.
e quaisquer desvios das opes padro durante o processo de instalao.
Immediately after the install video, there will be an document lecture
Imediatamente aps a instalao do vdeo, haver uma palestra do documento
with the installation instructions in tutorial format for those that prefer that approach.
com as instrues de instalao em formato tutorial para aqueles que preferirem essa abordagem.
You can choose either lecture, or both, to aid your installation on your system.
Voc pode escolher uma das palestras ou ambas para auxiliar sua instalao no seu sistema.
For those that prefer the complete and comprehensive videos showing each step
Para aqueles que preferem os vdeos completos e abrangentes
of the installation process for each tool, I have that covered in the bonus section of this course.
mostrando cada etapa do processo de instalao de cada ferramenta, eu cobri a seo bnus deste curso.